trustflowchecker.com 2018-10-30

# Privacy Policy | TrustFlowChecker.com

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.

We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.

We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.

We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.

Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.

We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through the TrustFlowChecker.com site, this information may be collected and used by others.

TrustFlowChecker.com may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party.

In addition, TrustFlowChecker.com may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. Such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to TrustFlowChecker.com, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

TrustFlowChecker.com will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on TrustFlowChecker.com or the site;
  * Protect and defend the rights or property of TrustFlowChecker.com (including enforcing this agreement); and,
  * Act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of TrustFlowChecker.com, or the public

**Tool Summary:** You can check the Privacy Policy of any URL with the **Privacy Policy**.

**Usage Tips:** Run this mass Privacy Policy tool for all your website's page.

|
